{
    "id": "45fd895af3e740048c98788b83b8be44",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. he is your friend, why doesn’t he talk to you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "569b36822ee849bdbdb7a5adad664205"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… it was a hot afternoon, I felt lethargic.",
            "description": "As shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e87f244625f54f5eb123c42be5b142ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. he is busy, he finds enough time for his family.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "035ee9d7a57141799bd2d49d66a64b9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will do it ……………………… it is dangerous.",
            "description": "Even though refers to the past even if refers to the present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "even though",
                "if",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "00cec70f28c44999a2a26fb240a18c06"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went alone ……………………. it was not safe.",
            "description": "Either even though or though is possible here. Even though is more emphatic than though.",
            "answers": [
                "even though",
                "even if",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6711559609cb451f94b065e1c9505522"
        },
        {
            "question": "He smiled ……………………… he knew everything.",
            "description": "Either as if or as though can be used to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "47b2850b88f34d0e86ce4b02bbeb1675"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will start …………………….. we hear from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "as soon as",
                "as far as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fbd22df4b834ce791a2285754dab42e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t leave ……………………. you give me my money back.",
            "description": "Unless means the same as if...not...",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e41b30e2a7eb4c14b894676a24606b87"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spent his last years in the village ……………………… he was born.",
            "description": "Where means the same as in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07163fbc5e9d48bf93e8a3be3cafcb95"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he is a popular actor, his acting skills are questionable.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5835b1cd37d4982a547438c441ae1a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He neither rose from his seat ……………………. looked at me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "702609f6fa244ecb85bb562ebc4ef490"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sounded ………………………. she was anxious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "though",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0bd3bababc954ba59e018aa9f9b61542"
        }
    ]
}